{
    "id": "c33e87206c32490f8bc16bfe582bdc04",
    "title": "Few Or Little",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have a ……………. friends in Malaysia.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "little",
                "less"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "144ec721ee3e4fc0b95022ce634de449"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has ..................... interest in politics.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "few",
                "a few"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "95d6e0909a014e22ac7311d37c3990ef"
        },
        {
            "question": "He won’t make a good teacher. He has very ………………… patience.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "little",
                "less"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ce8a90fdb0784445b18a7333c1666fb9"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is only a ………………. oil left.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "few",
                "little"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5b6dc477b69d4683b8200bdc88a8f524"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have visited Japan a …………… times.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "little",
                "less"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fb2a08c070d94cff8ccb32d40f946edf"
        },
        {
            "question": "I watched a ………………. films on the weekend.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "little",
                "less"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1352050d1e8e4700a96906ec120b21f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a busy executive. He has got very …………. spare time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "little",
                "less"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "efb6a29601aa4f06b0a52faf582dafee"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t think I will pass the test. I could answer only a ………………. questions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "little",
                "less"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f734b85268694977ba8499f0fd8891a9"
        },
        {
            "question": "His latest book was not a success. Only a ……………… copies were sold.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "little",
                "less"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "46c8327ade724a87beada2bbab38bfff"
        },
        {
            "question": "I only like a ………………. sugar in my tea.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "few",
                "less"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "eae15a8f6a1344f9972f02ecfc5c9d64"
        }
    ]
}